Southern New England Telephone Company Records
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series I: Administration/Business Records, undated, 1877-1980
  - Business - Corporation
    - Annual Reports - Regulatory Agencies
      - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1914-1920 (Box 6:, Folder 303-317)
      - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1921-1933 (Box 7:, Folder 318-342)
      - Federal Communications Commission, 1934-1938 (Box 7:, Folder 343-352)
      - Federal Communications Commission, 1939-1951 (Box 8:, Folder 353-378)
      - Federal Communications Commission, 1952-1963 (Box 9:, Folder 379-401)
      - Federal Communications Commission, 1964-1974 (Box 10:, Folder 402-423)
      - Federal Communications Commission, 1975-1983 (Box 11:, Folder 424-439)
      - Public Utilities Commission of CT, 1912-1916 (Box 11:, Folder 440-448)
      - New York Department of Public Service, 1930 (Box 12:, Folder 449)
        - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 12:, Folder 450)
      - New York Department of Taxation and Finance, 1933-1945 (Box 12:, Folder 451-463)
        - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 12:, Folder 464)
    - Annual Reports
      - AT&T Traveling Auditor's Reports, 1909-1928 (Box 12:, Folder 465-484)
      - AT&T Traveling Auditor's Reports, Additional Material (Box 13)
        - 1914 (Box 13:, Folder 485)
        - 1915 (Box 13:, Folder 486)
        - 1916 (Box 13:, Folder 487)
        - 1916-1917 (Box 13:, Folder 488)
        - 1919-1920 (Box 13:, Folder 489)
        - 1920-1921 (Box 13:, Folder 490)
        - 1921-1922 (Box 13:, Folder 491)
        - 1922-1923 (Box 13:, Folder 492)
        - 1924 (Box 13:, Folder 493)
        - 1925 (Box 13:, Folder 494)
        - 1926 (Box 13:, Folder 495)
        - 1927 (Box 13:, Folder 496)
        - 1928 (Box 13:, Folder 497)
        - 1929 (Box 13:, Folder 498)
        - 1930 (Box 13:, Folder 499)
        - 1931 (Box 13:, Folder 500)
      - Committee on Ecological Policy, 1974-1981 (Box 13:, Folder 501,502)
      - (Box 14:, Folder [empty])
      - (Box 15:, Folder [empty])
    - Capitol Stock Certificates - Farmington Valley Telephone Co., 1910-1938 (Box 16:, Folder 668)
    - Capitol Stock Certificates - SNET - Historical, 1882-1897 (Box 16:, Folder 669)
    - Capitol Stock Increases, 1900-1910 (Box 16:, Folder 670)
    - Capitol Stock - Employee's Stock Plan - Prospectus, 1964-1969 (Box 16:, Folder 671)
    - Capitol Stock - Employee's Stock Plan - Prospectus, 1970-1972, 1976-1977 (Box 16:, Folder 672)
    - Capitol Stock - Prospectus, 1953-1972 (gaps) (Box 16:, Folder 673)
    - Charter with Amendments, 1917-1978 (Box 16:, Folder 674)
    - Contracts and Agreements
      - American Bell Telephone Co., 1885 (Box 16:, Folder 675)
        - Contract 1326
        - Extra-territorial rights, State of CT
      - American Bell Telephone Co. and Lessees, 1880 (Box 16:, Folder 676)
        - Extra-territorial connecting lines
      - American Bell Telephone Co., Providence Telephone Co., 1902 (Box 16:, Folder 677)
        - Contract 544
        - Traffic agreement
      - American Telephone and Telegraph Co., 1918, 1931 (Box 16:, Folder 678)
        - Historical development of license contract with AT&T, 1965 (Box 16:, Folder 679)
        - License contract - supplemental letters and agreements, 1928-48 (Box 16:, Folder 680)
      - American Telephone and Telegraph Co., Western Union Telegraph Co., 1909-1915 (Box 16:, Folder 681)
        - Contract 1443, 1054
        - Joint use of facilities
      - American Union Telegraph Co., District Telephone Company of New Haven, undated, 1880 (Box 16:, Folder 682)
        - Contract 3959
        - Historical Papers
      - Anderson, Charles J., Bancroft, Ellen J., 1905-1921 (Box 16:, Folder 683)
        - Contract 994-997
        - Purchase of property - 124-126 Court St., New Haven
      - Baur, E., Metropolitan Body Co., 1890-1945 (Box 16:, Folder 684)
        - Contract 3060
        - Purchase of property - Federal and Charles St., Bridgeport
      - Canadian National Railway Co., 1923, 1959 (Box 16:, Folder 685)
        - Contract 4895
        - Standard telephone operating agreement
      - Canfield, W. - Canaan, 1898 (Box 16:, Folder 686)
        - Contract 930
        - Bill of sale to the Canaan Telephone Co.
      - Cincinnati and Suburban Bell Telephone Co., 1913 (Box 16:, Folder 687)
        - Contract 1320
        - Plan for employee's pension, disability benefits and Insurance
      - Coast Guard, 1917-1944 (Box 16:, Folder 688)
      - Connecticut Electric Companies, 1938-1947 (Box 16:, Folder 689)
        - Amendments, Cancellations
      - Connecticut District Telephone Co., District Telephone and Automatic Signal Co., 1879 (Box 16:, Folder 690)
        - Contract 1010
        - Guaranty to old company
      - Edwin Moss & Son Inc., 1957 (Box 16:, Folder 691)
        - Contract 4707
        - Construction 300 George St., New Haven
      - George B. H. MaComber Co., 1957 (Box 16:, Folder 692)
        - Contract 4685
        - 300 George St., New Haven
      - Huntington Telephone Co., 1943-1947 (Box 16:, Folder 693)
        - Contract 3855
        - Traffic agreement
      - Huntington Telephone Co., 1948 (Box 16:, Folder 694)
        - Contract 4110
        - Purchase of Huntington - agreement, bill of sale, assignment
      - Kirkham, G.C., East Haven Telephone and Electric Co., 1922-1947 (Box 16:, Folder 695)
        - Contract 2478
        - Purchase of East Haven Telephone & Electric Co.
      - Landmark Development Corp. of America, 1985-1986 (Box 16:, Folder 696)
        - Contract 6732
        - Real Estate Sales Agreement - 124-126 Court St. New Haven
      - Litchfield Telephone Co., 1881 (Box 16:, Folder 697)
        - Contract 4356
        - Certificate of Stock
      - New Canaan Fire Co., 1907, 1914 (Box 16:, Folder 698)
        - Contract 793
        - Fire alarm bell arrangement at central office
      - New England Telephone and Telegraph Co., 1948 (Box 17:, Folder 699)
        - Contract 4139
      - New England Telephone and Telegraph Co., 1952 (Box 17:, Folder 700)
        - Contract 4416
      - New York, New Haven, & Hartford Railroad Co., New England Telephone and Telegraph Co., 1948-1950 (Box 17:, Folder 701)
        - Contract 4128
      - New York, New Haven, & Hartford Railroad Co., 1959-61 (Box 17:, Folder 702)
        - Contract 4788
        - Standard Agreement
      - New York, New Haven, & Hartford Railroad Co., 1960 (Box 17:, Folder 703)
        - Contract 4853
        - Bill of sale - equipment
      - New York Telephone Co., 1948-49 (Box 17:, Folder 704)
        - Contract 4143
        - Division of Revenues
      - New York Telephone Co., 1959 (Box 17:, Folder 705)
        - Contract 4785
      - Outline of Compensation Agreements-Telephone and Telegraph Traffic, 1893-1942 (Box 17:, Folder 706)
      - Phelps, L.G., 1941-1942 (Box 17:, Folder 707)
        - Contract 3709 (no film)
        - Motion picture on the telephone in the defense program
      - Postal Telegraph and Cable Co., 1896 (Box 17:, Folder 708)
        - Contract 329
        - Hartford - sale of duct to postal in conduit
      - Postal Telegraph and Cable Co., 1901 (Box 17:, Folder 709)
        - Contract 499
        - Sale of duct in conduit
      - Postal Telegraph and Cable Co., 1912 (Box 17:, Folder 710)
        - Contract 1185
        - Use of duct - State St., New Haven
      - Postal Telegraph and Cable Co., 1913 (Box 17:, Folder 711)
        - Contract 1287
        - Use of duct - Ferry St., New Haven
      - Postal Telegraph and Cable Co., 1915 (Box 17:, Folder 712)
        - Contract 1479
        - Sale of duct - East Washington St., Norwalk
      - Postal Telegraph and Cable Co., 1928-1938 (Box 17:, Folder 713)
        - Contract 2963
      - Postal Telegraph and Cable Co., 1933 (Box 17:, Folder 714)
        - Contract 3302
        - Blanket agreement for joint use of 2 party poles
      - Providence Telephone Co., 1903 (Box 17:, Folder 715)
        - Contract 558
        - Service Between Pawcatuck and Westerly, Toll Business between Westerly-Stonington and Mystic
      - Union and New Haven Trust Co., 1901-1949 (Box 17:, Folder 716)
        - Contract 4332
      - United States Government, 1946-1950 (Box 17:, Folder 717)
        - Contract 4264
      - Various - 27 West St., Danbury, 1905 (Box 17:, Folder 718)
        - Contract 936-38, 940
        - Purchase of property
      - Waterbury Automatic Signal Telegraph Co., National Bell Telephone Co., 1880 (Box 17:, Folder 719)
        - Contract for exchanges
      - Western Electric Co., 1965 (Box 17:, Folder 720)
        - Historical development of supply contract
      - Western Electric Co., 1930-1973 (Box 17:, Folder 721)
        - Contract 1838
        - Supply contract
      - Western Electric Co., 1930-38 (Box 17:, Folder 722)
        - Standard supply contract
      - Western Electric Co., 1930-46 (Box 17:, Folder 723)
        - Standard Supply Contract
      - Western Union Telegraph Co., 1896 (Box 17:, Folder 724)
        - Contract 316
        - Sale of duct - Waterbury
      - Western Union Telegraph Co., 1900 (Box 17:, Folder 725)
        - Contract 472
        - Sale of duct - Derby
      - Western Union Telegraph Co., 1901 (Box 17:, Folder 726)
        - Contract 494
        - Sale of Duct - Norwich
      - Western Union Telegraph Co., 1958 (Box 17:, Folder 727)
        - Leasing of circuits between exchange areas
      - Western Union, 1971 (Box 17:, Folder 728)
        - Contract 5204
        - Sale of TWX service and equipment by Bell companies
      - Woodbury Telephone Co., 1961 (Box 17:, Folder 729)
        - Contract 4836
        - Mobile telephone service agreement
    - Minutes
      - [empty] (Box 18)
      - Officer's Meetings (conferences) (Box 19)
        - Index A - F (Box 19:, Folder 794)
        - Index G - Z (Box 19:, Folder 795)
        - 1967 (Box 19:, Folder 796)
        - 1971 (Box 19:, Folder 797)
        - 1972 (Box 19:, Folder 798)
        - 1973 (Box 19:, Folder 799)
        - 1974 (Box 19:, Folder 800)
        - 1975 (Box 19:, Folder 801)
        - 1976 (Box 19:, Folder 802)
      - Shareholder's Annual Meetings - Minutes and Exhibits
        - 1970 (Box 19:, Folder 808)
        - 1971 (Box 19:, Folder 809, 810)
        - 1972 April (Box 19:, Folder 811, 812)
        - 1972 June (Box 19:, Folder 813)
        - 1973 April (Box 19:, Folder 814)
        - 1973 August Shareholder's Special Meeting w/proxy ballot sample (Box 19:, Folder 815)
        - 1974 (Box 19:, Folder 816, 817)
        - 1975 (Box 19:, Folder 818-819)
        - 1976 (Box 20:, Folder 820-821)
    - Proxy Statement/ Notice of Annual Meetings, 1972-1994 (gaps) (Box 20:, Folder 848)
    - Quarterly Dividend, 1951-1981 (gaps) (Box 20:, Folder 849)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1976-1994 (gaps) (Box 20:, Folder 850)
    - Report of Annual Stockholders Meetings, 1964-1981 (Box 20:, Folder 851)
    - “Resolutions at Stockholders Meetings - 1882 - Present”, 1965 (Box 20:, Folder 852)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission - Form 10K, 1978, 1990-1996 (Box 20:, Folder 853-855)
    - Statistical Reports, 1970-1985 (gaps) (Box 20:, Folder 858)
    - Stockholders, 1882-1983 (Box 20:, Folder 859)
    - Stockholders - letters to, 1950-1983 (Box 20:, Folder 860)
  - Business - General
    - Copake Telephone Co. - notes, 1943-1952 (Box 20:, Folder 861)
    - “Data relating to the History, Business, and Financial Status of the Southern New England Telephone Co.”, 1945, 1948 (Box 20:, Folder 862)
    - Data and Information Systems (Information Technology Learning Center)
      see also Series V, Studies, Reports and Plans
      - Data Security Audit Committee, 1981 (Box 20:, Folder 866)
      - Fundamentals of #1 ESS, 1977 (Box 20:, Folder 872)
      - Guardsman Steering Committee - Minutes of meeting, 1981 (Box 20:, Folder 873)
      - IDP Accomplishments - First half of 1982 (Box 20:, Folder 874)
      - Information Systems Standards, 1980 (Box 20:, Folder 878, 879)
      - Information Technology Center Pamphlets, undated (Box 2:, Folder 881)
      - Introduction to the Teleprocessing Environment, undated (Box 2:, Folder 884)
      - Library Catalogs (Box 21)
        - Data Sources Catalog - Western Electric, 1980 (Box 21:, Folder 895)
        - On-line Database Guide, undated (Box 21:, Folder 900)
      - Programming in C: A Tutorial, 1974 (Box 21:, Folder 905)
      - Project Reference List, 1982 (Box 21:, Folder 906)
      - Response to the P.U.C.A. Audit, 1979 (Box 21:, Folder 907)
      - Total System Development Standards
        - Project Managing Manual, 1977 (Box 21:, Folder 908)
        - System Development Manual, 1977 (Box 21:, Folder 909)
        - Technical Procedures Manual (unrevised), 1978 (Box 21:, Folder 910)
        - Technical Procedures Manual (unrevised), 1978 (Box 21:, Folder 911)
    - Directory Assistance Charging
      see also series V: Studies, Reports and Plans
      - Correspondence and presentations, undated, 1975-1978 (Box 21:, Folder 916)
      - Directory Assistance Charging Working Committee, 1975 (Box 21:, Folder 917)
      - Directory Assistance Charging Working Committee, 1976-78 (Box 21:, Folder 918)
      - Informational material - binder, 1978 (Box 21:, Folder 919)
      - Other companies, undated, 1976-1978 (Box 21:, Folder 920)
      - Overview binder, 1978 (Box 21:, Folder 921, 922)
      - Planning documents, undated, 1973-1975 (Box 21:, Folder 923)
      - Position binder, 1978 (Box 22:, Folder 924)
      - PUCA docket #780534 - commission ordered documents, 1978? (Box 22:, Folder 925)
      - Statistics and working papers, undated, 1975-1978 (Box 22:, Folder 926)
    - Estimates - wire replacement, 1900 (Box 22:, Folder 928)
    - Expensing Station Connections
      - Backgrounder program for employees, 1981 (Box 22:, Folder 929)
      - DPUC filing binder - docket 800418, 1981 (Box 22:, Folder 930)
      - Expensing Station Connections Project Team, 1981 (Box 22:, Folder 931-932)
      - Expensing Station Connections Team Binder, 1981 (Box 22:, Folder 933-934)
      - Interview Guide, 1981 (Box 22:, Folder 935)
      - Stakeholder Interview Guide, 1981 (Box 22:, Folder 936-937)
      - Stakeholder Interview Guide - overheads, 1981 (Box 30:, Folder 938)
    - Farmington Valley Telephone Co., purchase of, 1939-1940 (Box 22:, Folder 939)
    - Farmington Valley Telephone Co., depreciation history, undated, 1940 (Box 22:, Folder 940)
    - Huntington Telephone Co. - purchase of, 1947-1948 (Box 22:, Folder 941)
    - Indentures, 1898? (Box 22:, Folder 942)
    - Kent Exchange, 1910-1918 (Box 22:, Folder 943, 944)
    - Operations
      see also: Series V: Studies, Plans and Reports
      - Analysis of Divestiture Impact, 1982 (Box 22:, Folder 945)
      - Docket 79-246 Revision to Interstate Private Line Tariff, 1980 (Box 22:, Folder 946)
      - Docket 79-246 Revision to Interstate Private Line Tariff, 1981 (Box 22:, Folder 947)
      - Interchange Agreement, 1982 (Box 22:, Folder 949)
      - License Contract (Value/Benefit Evaluation Forms), 1979-1980 (Box 23:, Folder 952)
      - License Contract, 1981 (Box 23:, Folder 953)
      - NERFAC Divestiture Issues, 1982 (Box 23:, Folder 954)
      - Network Planning and Industry Restructure- Competitive Strategies, 1981 (Box 23:, Folder 955)
      - Picture Phone Meeting Service, [1982?] (Box 23:, Folder 956)
        - Standard DS1/VF Interface, 1982 (Box 23:, Folder 957-958)
    - Personnel
      - Benefits Committee Minutes, 1912-1925 (Box 23:, Folder 959)
      - Employee Representation Plan, 1919 (Box 23:, Folder 984)
      - General, 1893-1920 (Box 23:, Folder 985)
      - Naples, T. Thrift Account, 1929 (Box 23:, Folder 988)
      - Personnel Planning Committee Network, 1979 (Box 23:, Folder 991)
      - Plan for Employees' Pensions, Disability, Benefits, and Death Benefits, 1937 (Box 23:, Folder 992)
      - Stock Plan (Employees), 1956 (Box 23:, Folder 993)
    - PreDecemberessor Companies - Stock Records, 1905-1948 (Box 23:, Folder 994)
    - Rate Cases
      - Connecticut PUC Findings and Orders in SNET Rate Cases, 1947-1982 (Box 23:, Folder 995-997)
      - Rate Case 1919 - Correspondence, 1918-1919 (Box 23:, Folder 998)
      - Rate Case 1927 - A History of the 1927 Rate Increase, 1928 (Box 30:, Folder 999)
      - Rate Case 1968 - Comptrollers Testimony and Exhibits (Box 23:, Folder 1000-1003)
      - 1968 Rate Case Pamphlets, undated (Box 23:, Folder 1004)
      - Rate Case 1972 - Interviewers Notebook and Publicity, 1969-1971 (Box 23:, Folder 1005)
      - Rate Case 1974
        - Possible Rate Case Intervenors - Northern Area, “What if?”, 1974? (Box 23:, Folder 1006)
        - Publicity, 1974 (Box 23:, Folder 1007)
      - Rate Case 1977 - Master Binder (Box 24:, Folder 1008, 1009)
      - Rate Case 1978 - News Coverage, 1977 (Box 24:, Folder 1010)
      - Rate Case 1980
        - Decemberision and Implementation, 1980 (Box 24:, Folder 1011)
        - Employee Background Package (OS), 1980 (Box 30:, Folder 1012)
        - Information Committee - General Binder, 1980 (Box 24:, Folder 1013, 1014)
        - Media Relations Plan, 1980 (Box 24:, Folder 1015)
        - Public Relations - Background Information for Rate Case Testimony, 1980 (Box 24:, Folder 1016)
        - Rate Case 1980, Book 1 (Box 24:, Folder 1017, 1018)
        - Rate Case 1980, Book 2 (Box 24:, Folder 1019, 1020)
        - 1980 Report: Rate Request - presentation binder - copy 1 (Box 24:, Folder 1021)
        - 1980 Report: Rate Request - presentation binder - copy (Box 24:, Folder 1022)
      - Rate Case 1982
        - Advertising testimony, 1982 (Box 24:, Folder 1023)
        - Backgrounder program for employees - leaders guide, 1982 (Box 24:, Folder 1024)
        - Binder, 1982 (Box 544:, Folder 1025)
        - Civil Action B75319 - transcript, 1979 (Box 544:, Folder 1026, 1027)
        - Civil Action B75319 - transcript day 16, 1979 (Box 25:, Folder 1028, 1029)
        - Civil Action B75319 - summation of counsel and jury instruction on damage, 1980 (Box 25:, Folder 1030)
        - Civil Action B75319 - verdict, 1979 (Box 25:, Folder 1031)
        - “Coming Up: 1982 Rate Case” - interview binder (Box 544:, Folder 1032)
        - “Coming Up: 1982 Rate Case” - presentation binder (Box 544:, Folder 1033)
        - News conference binder, 1982 (Box 544:, Folder 1034)
        - Pamphlets, 1982 (Box 544:, Folder 1035)
        - Public Relations Department - Resource document binder, 1981 (Box 544:, Folder 1036)
    - Sharon Telephone Company - Purchase of TWX Sale, 1939-44 (Box 25:, Folder 1037)
      - AT&T Letter and SNET Related Memorandum - vol. 1, 1969-1972 (Box 25:, Folder 1038, 1039)
      - AT&T Letter and SNET Related Memorandum - vol. 2, 1971-1972 (Box 25:, Folder 1040, 1041)
      - Journal Entries, 1971 (Box 25:, Folder 1042-1044)
      - Journal Entries - final, 1971 (Box 25:, Folder 1045, 1046)
      - SNET Task Force, 1970 (Box 25:, Folder 1047)
      - Studies
        - Special Study of Teletypewriter Investments, vol. 1, 1967 (Box 25:, Folder 1048, 1049)
        - Special Study of Teletypewriter Investments, vol. 2, 1967 (Box 25:, Folder 1050, 1051)
        - Study of Certain Investments in the Teletypewriter Station Apparatus Account, 1969 (Box 25:, Folder 1052, 1053)
        - Teletypewriter Exchange Service - Special Study Status Report, 1969 (Box 26:, Folder 1054, 1055)
        - TWX Sale Study - Minor Materials Costs, 1969-1970 (Box 26:, Folder 1056)
        - The TWX Coordinator Publication, 1971 (Box 26:, Folder 1057)
        - TX 600 Series Study, 1969-1970 (Box 26:, Folder 1058)
      - TWX Sale Binders, 1969-1971
        - Book 1 (Box 26:, Folder 1059-1064)
        - Book 2 (Box 26:, Folder 1065-1066)
        - Book 3 (Box 26:, Folder 1067-1068)
      - TWX Sale (Box 26:, Folder 1069)
        - Book 1
        - Book 2 (Box 27:, Folder 1070, 1071)
        - Book 3 (Box 27:, Folder 1072)
      - TWX Sale Manual, Book 1, 1970-1971 (Box 28:, Folder 1073, 1074)
      - TWX Sale Manual, Book 2, 1970-1971 (Box 28:, Folder 1075, 1076)
      - TWX Sale Manual, TS 8.10-10.40, 1969-1970 (Box 28:, Folder 1077)
      - TWX Tertiary Switching Plan, 1970 (Box 28:, Folder 1078)
      - TWX Transfer Committee - Minutes, 1969-1971 (Box 28:, Folder 1079, 1080)
      - TWX Transfer Guidelines, 1971 (Box 28:, Folder 1081)
    - Westerly Automatic Telephone Co., proposed purchase of, 1944-1945, 1961 (Box 29:, Folder 1082)
    - Work Orders (fragile), 1912-1916 (Box 29:, Folder 1083)
  - OVERSIZED
    - Executive Office Post Cards (fragile), 1905-1917 (Box 30:, Folder 151)
    - Executive Office Post Cards, 1907-1918 (Box 30:, Folder 152)
    - Executive Office Post Cards, 1907-1918 (Box 30:, Folder 153)
    - Executive Office Telephone Club Charter Member List, 1905 (Box 30:, Folder 160)
    - Executive Office Telephone Directory Cover Sample, 1919 (Box 30:, Folder 162)
    - Stakeholder Interview Guide - Overheads, 1981 (Box 30:, Folder 938)
    - Rate Case 1927 - “A History of the 1927 Rate Increase”, 1928 (Box 30:, Folder 999)
    - Rate Case 1980 - Employee Bakcground Package (Box 30:, Folder 1012)
- Series II: Accounting / Finance Records, 1882-1985
  - Alex, A.J. Chief Accountant, Comptrollers Office
    - Administration Building Refurbishment, 1938-1947; 1.01-1.05 (Box 31:, Folder 1084)
    - Holiday Pay, 1952; 1.06 (Box 31:, Folder 1085)
    - Advertising, 1934-1941; 2.02-2.04 (Box 31:, Folder 1086)
    - Accounting Department Space, 1946; 2.05
    - Army and Navy Coastal Defense Calls, 1942; 3-3.02 (Box 31:, Folder 1087)
    - Military Correspondence, 1943-1951; 4-4.03 (Box 31:, Folder 1088)
    - Technical Correspondence, 1950; 5.0 (Box 31:, Folder 1089)
    - Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company, 5.01 (Box 31:, Folder 1090)
      - Michigan Bell Telephone Company
      - Southwestern Bell Telephone Company
      - Wisconsin Bell Telephone Company, 1937-1939
    - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, 1930; 5.01 (Box 31:, Folder 1091)
    - Banking Correspondence, 1926-1951; 6.01-6.03 (Box 31:, Folder 1092)
    - Worker's Compensation and Employee Benefits, 1946; 7.01 (Box 31:, Folder 1093)
    - Monthly Billing Benefits, 1948; 8.01 (Box 31:, Folder 1094)
    - Billing, 1922; 8.02 (Box 31:, Folder 1095)
    - Centralizing, 1921; 8.03
    - Radio Broadcasting Billing, 1923; 8.04
    - Plant Charges, 1921; 8.05
    - Billing, 1925-1928; 8.06
    - Radio Billing, 1937; 8.07
    - Telegraph Billing, 1930; 8.08
    - Maintenance and Facilities Billing, undated; 8.09
    - Gasoline Billing, 1925; 8.10
      - Duplicate Billing, 1926
      - Medical Billing, 1934
    - Rates and Billing, 1923; 8.11 (Box 31:, Folder 1096)
    - Rates and Billing, Zone Registration, Correspondence and Exhibits, 1930; 8.12
    - Contracts with US Government, 1937; 8.14
    - Billing with US Government, Correspondence, Exhibits, 1937; 8.141
    - Government Billing, 1937; 8.142
    - Billing with US Navy, Correspondence, Exhibits, 1924-1944; 8.143
    - Billing with US Army, 1944; 8.144
    - Billing with US Government concerning Social Security Costs, 1937; 8.145
    - Independent Telephone Company Billing, 1936-1946; 8.15 (Box 31:, Folder 1097)
      - Billing of PBX Engineering, 1936
      - Billing of Administration Expense, 1935
    - Billing Procedure, 1937; 8.16 (Box 31:, Folder 1098)
    - ABX Billing, 1938; 8.17
    - Employee Billing, 1938; 8.18
    - Billing and Plant Engineering, 1936; 8.19
    - Billing for Advertising and Electronics, 1940; 8.20
    - Joint Pole Line Billing, 1931-1940; 8.21
    - Billing and Commercial Practices, 1946; 8.22 (Box 31:, Folder 1099)
    - Billing and Toll Services, Exhibits, 1941; 8.23
    - Field Checking and Joint Pole Maintenance Billing, 1941; 8.24
    - Auditor Bills, 1938; 8.25
    - Joint Poll Billing, 1931; 8.26 (Box 31:, Folder 1100)
    - Contract Work Billing, 1931; 8.27